

BOLARINWA AHMED Frontend Developer

- 12, Nwachukwu promise ave, Onihale extension, Ilepa, 112104 Ifo, Nigeria
- bolarinwaahmed22@gmail.com
- **** 08026117966
- in Ahmed Bolarinwa
- https://github.com/Bola-coder

Profile

I am a Frontend Developer with 2+ years of experience developing responsive websites and web apps. I have worked on projects ranging from E-commerce websites to clones of popular websites using frontend technologies and I am well versed with the integration of third party APIs into my Apps.

I am proficient in turning designs to code and I am always ready to learn new technologies to solve problems.

Professional Experience

01/2022 – present

Abeokuta Ogun State,

Nigeria

05/2021 – 09/2021

Lagos, Nigeria

Frontend Developer (Siwes Intern), Africa Trainovation Consulting

Frontend Bootcamp, Zuri Technologies

Skills

Frontend Web Development ● ● ● ● HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React,, Bootstrap, Styled

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React,, Bootstrap, Styled-Component

Backend Development

Nodejs, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, Firebase

Languages

English • • • • • Yoruba • • • •

Interests

Web3, FinTech, EduTech, AgroTech

Projects

Sneaker, An E-commerce web-app where users can view and add sneakers to cart. A project in progress.

Texchange, A simple web app that convert currency to another specified currency

Planktops, A simple website for a furniture business

Netflix Clone, A clone of the popular Netflix website with movies being fetch from TMDB API

Education

09/2019 – present

Babcock University, Computer Science